<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="medical_disclaimer">Do not use this diet without consulting your doctor or appropriate medical professional. I am not licensed or trained by any medical, weight loss or dieting institution.
        The diet given here is not meant to treat or cure any specific health condition. The diet plan given here is my personal dieting strategy deployed in a friendly user interface.
        The strategy in this app should not replace or supersede any care direction you receive from your healthcare provider. You must exercise caution and common sense"</string>
    <string name="input_instructions">Yes means you met this levels challenge plus all previous. No means you failed this levels challlenge only. Backslide means you broke previous rules.
            You can only have 3 no answers and 1 backslide in your 60 yes streak. If you take a vacation or have a special event just skip your diet for the day!</string>

    <!-- Titles -->

    <string name="title_zero">Introduction</string>
    <string name="title_one">Morning liquid</string>
    <string name="title_two">Midday liquid</string>
    <string name="title_three">Evening liquid</string>
    <string name="title_four">Morning Meals</string>
    <string name="title_five">Midday Meals</string>
    <string name="title_six">Evening Meals</string>


    <!-- Rules -->
    <string name="rules_zero">The plan is to remove processed food from your diet.
                This will be done in very small steps so you can adjust your mind and lifestyle easily.
                Each level increases the challenge and you must keep performing the old rules as well.
                So what can you eat?!?
                You can eat whatever you prefer, but you must buy ingredients found in nature.
                If you couldn\'t go into the wilderness/farm and collect the ingredients then they are not acceptable
                Further you cannot use mechanical food processing equipment. Or ask/pay someone else to do so for you.
                Exclusions include: cuts of meat, milk, or zero cal sauces. No honey or zero calorie sweetener.
                Example: If you want bread you must grind the flour from wheat and bake it.(You wont and that\'s the point)
                There will be special allowances and rewards along the way"</string>
    <string name="rules_one">No processed drink ingredients during morning period. Homemade zero calories drink such as coffee or tea allowed. 2 spoonfuls of milk maximum. No store bought zero calories drinks that have flavor. Sparkling water is OK.</string>
    <string name="rules_two">Previous rules extended to include mid day period. </string>
    <string name="rules_three">Previous rules extended to include evening period. You will not be having processed liquids for the remainder of the diet </string>
    <string name="rules_four">You must now exclude processed food ingredients during the morning period. This is in addition to existing rules of not consuming processed liquids </string>
    <string name="rules_five">Previous rules extended to include mid day period. </string>
    <string name="rules_six">revious rules extended to include evening period. </string>


    <!-- Rewards -->

    <string name="reward_zero">none</string>
    <string name="reward_one">A teaspoon of pure honey with your morning drink (limit 1 per day). FYI a teaspoon is &#8531; of the average spoon used to eat</string>
    <string name="reward_two">An additional drink with a teaspoon of pure honey on top of your previous allowance raising your total to 2 per day. Both can now be consumed at any time.</string>
    <string name="reward_three">You may consume flavored zero calorie drinks. Along with your 2 sweetened drink allowances from previous rules.</string>
    <string name="reward_four">You may use low calorie sauce or seasoning. A low calorie sauce is a sauce that adds less than 50 calories to a plate of food. Typically there is less than 1 gram of added sugar on label.</string>
    <string name="reward_five">You may treat yourself to a small store bought processed food item. The food item must be no bigger than your smartphone</string>
    <string name="reward_six">Bravo, your done. Your reward is better probability of positive health outcomes</string>


    <!-- Links -->

    <string name="link_zero"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/S5DI_52xBR0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_one"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pCKGWQ5MUV4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_two"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pCKGWQ5MUV4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_three"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pCKGWQ5MUV4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_four"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w3fY-qw1U3U" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_five"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w3fY-qw1U3U" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>
    <string name="link_six"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w3fY-qw1U3U" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></string>

    <string name="settings_explain">You can set a reminder to input your days results and specify when each period ends</string>

</resources>